let questions;

var questions = [
  {
    // Question 1
    question: "1.What sort of animal is Walt Disney's Dumbo?",
    answers: {
      a: "Deer",
      b: "Rabbit",
      c: "Elephant",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    // Question 2
    question: "2.What was the name of the Spanish waiter in the TV sitcom "Fawlty Towers"?",
    answers: {
      a: "Manuel",
      b: "Pedro",
      c: "Alfonso",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 3
    question: "3.Which battles took place between the Royal Houses of York and Lancaster?",
    answers: {
      a: "Hundred Years War",
      b: "English Civil War",
      c: "War of the Roses",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    // Question 4
    question: "4.Which former Beatle narrated the TV adventures of Thomas the Tank Engine?",
    answers: {
      a: "John Lennon",
      b: "Ringo Starr",
      c: "Paul McCartney<",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 5
    question: "5. What fake name does Phoebe use when she wants to remain anonymous?",
    answers: {
      a: "Regina Phalange",
      b: "Bonnie Riddle",
      c: "Anastasia Beaverhausen",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 6
    question: "6. Monica and Chandler met on Thanksgiving in 1987. She pursued her career as a chef because Chandler complimented her on which dish?",
    answers: {
      a: "Mac & Cheese",
      b: "Stuffing",
      c: "Green Bean Casserole",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 7
    question: "7. When Ross and Rachel were 'on a break,' Ross slept with Chloe. Where does she work?",
    answers: {
      a: "Domino's",
      b: "Xerox",
      c: "Microsoft",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 8
    question: "8. What’s Joey’s penguin’s name?",
    answers: {
      a: "Huggsy",
      b: "Waddle",
      c: "Snowflake",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 9
    question: "9. Janice gets married twice. What’s was her first husband’s name?",
    answers: {
      a: "Chandler Bing",
      b: "Gary Litman",
      c: "Rob Baileystock",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 10
    question: "10. What’s the name of the 1950s-themed diner where Monica worked as a waitress?",
    answers: {
      a: "Marilyn & Audrey",
      b: "Central Perk",
      c: "Moondance Diner",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
]